P. Diddy's homes were raided in both Los Angeles and Miami.
I guess the federal agents were mad because he's flagrant,
tapped a cell and a phone in the basement.
His team was not supreme.
The raids were part of an ongoing investigation involving Homeland Security.
Law enforcement sources suggest that the case may be tied
to sex trafficking allegations against Puff Daddy.
Footage shows individuals, including his sons,
Justin and King Combs, in handcuffs near the property.
The word about it is that apparently he escaped
and flew away in a private jet that landed in Antigua and Barbuda.
But I just want to say this, but I'm unlikable!
Listen, Black media went in on me, but they have stayed away from him.
I've only been to one Puff Daddy party in my life.
And it was, no, because I'm not that kind of girl.
I say, it's time to go.
You never party with me, Amanda.
You never party with me.
I genuinely was like, I got to get out of here.
I couldn't get service to call an Uber.
So I was literally just like stuck in the hills.
And I was about to start walking.
And then flipping Jesse Smollett pulled up because he had a car that was waiting for him.
And so he pulled up in the escalator and was like,
are you trying to leave?
And I was like, get me out of here!
So shout out to Jesse.
I should probably, is he in jail?
I should probably put something in this commissary for that ride.
We are, we are, we are.